we were basically deployed in the occupied
нас в основном выставили на захваченных
territories there to protect public
территориях там для охраны общественной
safety, I understood
безопасности понял там
there and there
туда-сюда
I’ll be dressed up like it’s unrealistically cool
буду нарядился нереально прикольно
Nice hello bu priko Where are you from Good
Здорово Здрав бу прико Ты откуда Добрый
fellow
молодец
Sochi Sochi fat nights [ __ ] fat eyes
Сочи Сочи жирные ночи бля жирные очи
it was you who was a vdvshnika or whoever you were Well
это ты был вдвшника или кем ты был Ну
google crapo neshka I’m not  I know I don’t see the
загугли крапо нешка я не знаю я не вижу
speck It’s
крап Там
dark there Well, you google it, type in the capo
темно Ну ты загугли набери крапо
vest capo The vest is a [ __ ] yes
тельняшка крапо Тельняшка ор ебанашка да
bro Well listen, you’re an adequate guy,
братан Ну слушай ты же адекватный мужик
okay let’s talk about who you
нормально поговорим реально кем ты
were in the sense of Who I was, well, in the army I was
был в смысле Кем я был ну в армии Я был
a private in the army, not Well, this is the capo
армии рядовым не Ну вот это крапо
vest  sailor pilot there is infantry who
тельняшка моряк лётчик там пехота кто
is not this is the Russian Guard Russian Guard And like, they
нет это росгвардия росгвардия А типа
dispersed rallies, yes, like, let me be
разгоняли митинги да типа
in Moscow for Uraza Bayram I
дай-то в Москве был на Ураза Байрам Я
was at the Confederation Cup, I understood And
был на кубке конфедерации я был понял А
this is when you dispersed a rally in
это когда разгонял ты митинг в
Moscow in the year 1977, probably in
Москве в году в семнадцатом наверное в
1977 Cool A type  beat with
семнадцатом Прикольно А типа бил
batons Like you beat these people there,
дубинками Типа вы там били этих людей да
like no, you can’t, you can’t, like they
типа нет нельзя же нельзя ну типа там
were pushing back with shields
щитами отталкивались
at me, no, it wasn’t like that And I do
именно в меня нет не было такого А в
n’t remember that from friends to colleagues to colleagues either Well,
в сослуживцев тоже не помню такого Ну
they just told this story that they
просто рассказывали такую историю что
provoked them there specifically when the
там провоцировали специально когда вот л
Confederacy  there was a Confederation Cup there
Конфедерации был там кубок Конфедерации
- that’s
- это
what, well, it’s a football match, I
что ну это футбольный матч же
understand Pony, but now you also serve in this one,
понял Поня а а сейчас ты тоже в этой
and in this one in the Russian Guard, it’s not
служишь да в этой в росгвардии
me who came home on vacation. And where did I
не я же в отпуск приехал домой А откуда
come from on
приехал в
vacation from you? Well, where
отпуск от вас Ну откуда
exactly I can’t do this normally
именно я не могу такое шение нормально
in any case, in different regions you
по-любому в разных есть регионах
film, you film, I don’t, I don’t film, I’m still
снимаешь ты снимаешь не не снимаю я все
like this I go out In short, to drive, I work as a
так Выхожу Короче погнать я работаю
programmer, I sometimes go out in the evenings
программистом я вечерами иногда выхожу
Just to drive the stream, in short, men
Просто чтоб погнать потка короче мужиков
T all sorts of
Т всяких я
annealing, well, we were basically deployed
отжига ну нас нас в основном выставили
in the occupied territories there to
на захваченных территориях там для
protect public safety  I understood
охраны общественной безопасности понял
back and forth what kind of public
там туда-сюда какая там общественная
safety there is. Maybe there’s everything like the
безопасность Может там же всё типа
military there, what else to exhibit there, I
военные есть что там ещё выставлять не
can’t understand, well, the people of Shuya also seem to be
могу понять ну люди же Шуе тоже как бы
protesting there in the sense of who is protesting
там протестуют в смысле а кто протестует
in the occupied
на захваченных
territories, people who didn’t didn’t want
территориях люди которые не не хотели
who Well, to be captured
которые Ну чтобы их захватывали
you understand
понимаешь
and what did you do with them, beat
и что вы с ними делали били
them? No, of course,
их Да нет конечно ты
what are you doing? Well, no, I don’t understand. And where, well, I didn’t see that there
что Ну не Поня А где вот ну я не видел
were any protests in the occupied territories,
чтобы на захваченных территориях были
where we have no protests,
протесты где у нас протестов нету
no protests, just so that there
протестов нету Просто для того чтобы там
would be order somewhere  here in remote places
был порядок где-то вот в местах
[ __ ], I haven’t heard that in short there on their own
Бля я е слышал что короче там на сво вот
these Chechens are stupidly building everyone shorter than the
эти чеченцы тупо строят всех короче
Russian National Guard not the Russian Guard It’s not
русских росгвардия не росгвардия Да не
like they want checkpoints they come
что они типа хотят блокпосты приезжают
there give these Russian boys if they
там дают этим русским пацанам если они
want Let them [ __ ] No we were originally there I
хотят Пускай еба Нет мы изначально я там
was there I know  if they want, get out of here, I
был я знаю они если хотят идите отсюда
understand, you're afraid of
понял ты боишься
the Chechens,
чеченцев
no, I gave lei to the
нет давал лей
Chechens, it was a matter of urgency, of urgency, he
чеченцам было дело по срочке по срочке
built them,
строил их
like, no, it's not like he built them, just one on
типа нет не то что строил просто один на
me, like, go there, I told you, I
меня типа иди туда я тебе сказал я
Speak, can you hear, shut your mouth,
Говори Слышишь ты рот закрой свой язык
put your tongue in, I'm from Siberia  you're saying
свой засунь я с Сибири ты говорю вообще
who he is
кто такой он
I'm a master of sports in
я мастер спорта по
Dagestan in wrestling I'm saying I don't give a [ __ ]
Дагестан по борьбе Я говорю Да мне похуй
I'll take a stick in your belly now I'll stick you in the belly
Я сейчас палку возьму теб в пузо воткну
talk What are you going to do
говор Что ты сделаешь
you
ты ему
dragged him in well I've come to my senses I do
втащил ну пону дал в себя пришёл Поня
n't think it was possible to fight there bro
там там драться нельзя было братан там
when I served  in the Senate year there,
когда я служил в сенатом году там понял
everyone understood that everyone was
каждый синя каж
immediately called in.
сразу вызывали
It’s true that they say that Ramzan
Вот правда говорят что там Рамзан
Kadyrov is there. In short, if someone there
Кадыров Короче если кто-то там чеченцу
slaps a Chechen in the face, he will come and give something like
даст пощёчину приедет и даст типа
that Yes, no, of course, well, you’re afraid of
тому Да нет конечно ну ты боишься
Kadyrov. Why should I be
Кадырова А почему мне я должен его
afraid of him? Well, they say, Well, I  I heard that
бояться Ну вот говорят Ну я слышал что
he, in short, makes all Russians
он короче всех русских заставляет
afraid of the
бояться
Chechens No, they are undoubtedly
чеченцев Нет они бесспорно они бесспорно
very hot people by blood, they
очень горячие люди по крови они в
basically don’t think about anything if they are
основном ни о чём не думают если их
hooked by something Yes Bazaar no, they
что-то зацепило Да Базару нет они
twitch But mostly it’s like
дёргаются Но в основном как
I don’t know, well, you too  Slav
бы я не знаю ну ты же тоже славянин
Slav b Yes, we are also godfather, yes we are
славянин б Да свя мы же тоже да мы же
also bro We are too Well, how can I say, we
тоже братан Мы же тоже Ну ну как сказать
won’t just stand when they
стоять не будем просто когда Нас
beat us We are also godfather Well, look, I
бьют Мы же тоже кум Ну как Смотри я
saw for example, in short, there is some
видел например короче там какой-то
guy who in Volgograd prepared the Koran for
парень который в Волгограде Коран подг
him.
его
In short, they arrested him, but he was not taken in
вя короче арестовали но его забрали не
Volgograd, but in Chechnya, they took him to Chechnya
Волгограде су А в Чечню отвезли в Чечне
in a pre-trial detention center, in short, this Kadyrov brought
в СИЗО короче прил этот Кадыров привёз
his piston,
своего пистона
this Adam Kadyrov, in short, a
этого этого Адама Кадырова короче
little Russian boy, a
мало русского пацана
Slav, on camera, kicking from his knees,
славянина на камеру ногами с колена
in short, with
короче
his hands, he said nothing from his throat,
руками из глотну
Okay, they are coming here They are
промолчали О'кей они приезжают сюда Они
here  They get it, we come
тут ются Они же получают мы приезжаем
there, we get it there, don’t look, they don’t,
туда мы там получаем не не смотри они не
too, they brought a Russian from Volgograd.
тоже они привезли русского из Волгограда
Yes, and they showed on camera that they don’t
Да и на камеру показали что они его пи
understand him directly, little pi, and you think there
прямо понимаешь мало пи а ты думаешь тут
are no such options, why didn’t you see the video
нету таких вариантов че не видел видео
so they took it and showed how  not a
чтоб взяли и показали как чеченца ни
single video of a Chechen
одного видео
Yes, I personally, it’s just not like without a camera
Да я лично вот просто без камеры не так
without a camera, and they specially filmed it on
без камеры а они специально сняли на
camera and showed it. They
камеру показали сри Они специально
filmed it on purpose, and why didn’t the Russians
снимают и и почему русские не
stand up for this guy? He’s still
заступились за этого парня Он до сих пор
there in Grozny in a pre-trial detention center and his posh
там в Грозном в СИЗО и его пош каждый
comes every day
день приходит сын
Kadyrov’s son is killing a Russian
Кадырова убивают русского
Slav here I’m especially in such a situation, this is the situation
славянина тут я особо такой ситуации
I’ll tell you this here, too, as if the
я тебе так скажу тут тоже как бы
Caucasian there, the Dagestan
кавказской там дагестанской там
nationality there generally treats people with
национальности вообще к людям с
caution,
осторожностью
so I’m not talking about that, in short,
относится так я не про то короче имею в
I mean, I think why the Russians if they’re
виду я и думаю почему русские если они
something-  then they allow if they
что-то допускают если они что-то
allow something here too [ __ ] Po You’re a
допускает тоже тут Бля По Вот ты
Slav,
славянин
yes yes Well, why don’t you stand up for the
да да Ну почему ты не вступаешь за
Slav who is being beaten in
славянина того которого бьют в
Grozny Well, now, probably the time is such
Грозном Ну сейчас наверное время такое
that there’s no need for the VPR of a Slav for a
что что типа не надо ВПР славянина за
Slav
славянина
Well, that’s it, it’s ours  the
Да ну ти раз раз раз наше
government is fighting against our brothers,
правительство воюет против наших братьев
well, look, if they say the Russians
ну так смотри если говорят русские своих
don’t abandon their own, yes And here, in short, the Chechens
не бросают да А тут короче чеченцы
in Grozny are like Russian, too,
короче в Грозном типа русс же тоже
Russia Bro, yes, but they are not Russian, so it
Россия Братан да но они не русские так
turns out that the Russians abandoned their own, well,
типа русские получается своих бросили ну
how can I tell you that they are not Russian, they are Russian too
как как тебе сказать не русские они тоже
No, they’re not Russian, but this is Russia.
это Нет они не русские но это Россия Да
Yes, well, in short, yes. That is, they can be Russian, so it turns out. Well, no, no, no, no,
так получается Ну нет нет нет нет нет
no. It’s like, it’s going to take a long time
нет нет Там типа долго
to figure out who. Why should we
разбираться Кто Зачем чего
harness the kid to a kid? Yes, he’s Russian,
ко за пацанчика тно впрячь Да он русский
but let him Why would my bro be on
но пусть его Почему был бы мой братан
tour?  I would tear up and throw this situation
туре рвал бы и метал я эту ситуацию
In general, I’m hearing this for the first time Yes yes Well, look
Вообще первый раз слышу Да да Ну смотри
here it’s not like bro for bro It’s
тут не то что братан за братана Тут
Russian for
русский за
Russian Well, of course you
русского Ну и ты меня конечно
pulled me up I can’t answer for the whole people, sconce
подтянул Я за весь народ не могу
this situation is the first time it’s
отвечать бра эту ситуацию первый раз это
at a rally in short to disperse the people  it’s
на митинге короче разгонять народ это
possible it’s just yes And for a Russian I do
можно это просто да А за русского за не
n’t know, but it’s weak to stand up for a Russian
знаю не был а за русского заступиться
Yes why weakly No not weak at all
слабо Да почему слабо Нет вообще не
Well, let’s stand up for
слабо Ну вот давай заступится се за
Nikita
Никиту
Ravel, you’ll say
равеля скажешь
that Well, this one whom
что Ну вот этот которого сейчас в
you can go out to now in Grozny and what And what
Грозном можешь выйти а что А что он
did he do  And what did he do? I’m telling you, he
сделал А что он сделал Я тебе говорю он
set fire to the Koran in Volgograd,
в Волгограде поджёг Коран
he set fire to the Koran.
был он поджёг Коран
Yes, I won’t. What’s wrong with him? He’s Russian,
Да я не буду А что так его он русский
let him be judged according to the law.
пусть его судят по зако это
Wait, this is religious value, this is their
это подожди религиозная ценность это их
God, this is their Faith, and condemn this,
Бог это их Вера и осуждать это
these are the boys who burned the Bible.  and
это пацаны которые спалили Библию и их
no one of them Who said Well, over there on the grill,
никто Кто сказал Ну вон на мангале
the boys burned the Bible in short and
пацаны Библию были сожгли короче и
nothing, no one of them but Russian For the Koran
ничего никто их не а русского За Коран
In short, I
Короче я
understood if I saw Pony In short, I
понял если бы я увидел Поня Короче я
understood Like, in general, jump in short on the
понял Типа в общем прыгать короче на
Ramza
рамза
T honestly, I’m honestly, I’m honestly for peace
Т честно я честно я честно я за мир
Zamir and the rest is there the Koran the Bible there
Замир а остальное там Коран Библия там
Iwu or
Иу или
Allah if Allah or Jesus There it’s like I’m
Аллах если Аллах или Иисус Там как бы я
for everyone, that is, well, it didn’t all come from me,
за всех то есть ну это не от меня всё
you know, I don’t wish harm on anyone, you
пошло понимаешь я я никому зла не желаю
know
понимаешь
Okay,
Ладно
let’s just find a letter on my Telegram
давай застал просто пись на мий Telegram
right now axis VN
прям зараз ось ВН
apok  It’s even more and more respectful YouTube has occupied
апок це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube заня
us through the skarg ORV in your ban and even more
нас через скарг ОРВ в твый бан и дуже
videos I don’t show people often I don’t
багато вдео не показую людям вчасно не
show information about streams in order to make
показуе информация про стримы тому для
Mali an operational link to
того щоб ми Мали оперативный звязок
write right away and while there in
пишиться прямо зараз а пок там в
telegram okrim video sche tezh tsikava and
телеграми окрим видео ще теж цикава и
korisna  information and mi vinni z you
корисна информация и ми повинни з вами
trimati postiyny operational connection
тримати постийний оперативный звязок
nezalezhno in that chi show you the process
незалежно в того чи покаже вам проце
YouTube Slava ukraini pis
YouTube Слава украини пись